Ana Bogatinovska

+38972207429 bogatinovska.ana@gmail.com Web Presence
LinkedIn
Github
Ana's Personal Portfolio & Resume

Ana Bogatinovska Software Engineer

ABOUT ME

I am eagerly motivated to continue advancing in my career. I have gained really valuable experience collaborating with diverse teams. My passion is continuous learning and problem-solving. I can take new challenges with enthusiasm and can easily adapt to changes.

So far, my experiences have improved my technical skills, as well as my ability to collaborate effectively with the team and handle different work situations. Ultimate goal is to work on digital projects that make a big, positive impact.

SKILLS

- Javascript, Typescript, Angular 13+, Dart, Flutter, Ionic Framework, Vuejs, Quasar Framework
- AWS Amplify Auth, Rxjs, Fuse Angular Template, Tailwind, Angular Material, YouTrack, Trello GitHub, GraphQL
- NgRx Store, MongoDb, LocalStorage, Vuex store

EXPERIENCE

MFactor Consultancy - Melbourne, Australia — *Software Engineer*

December 2021 - present (Remote)

- Developed user-friendly responsive web & mobile interfaces
- Code reviews, identify bugs, implement necessary fixes and improvements
- Close communication with backend developers and designers
- Skills: Javascript, TypeScript, Angular 13+, Angular Material, Tailwind, Fuse Angular, Flutter, Ionic Framework, GitHib, YouTrack, Trello, Vue 2, RxJs, NgRx Store, Vuex Store

Musala Soft - Skopje, North Macedonia— Junior Software Engineer

- Worked on company internal web application
- Involved in a project for developing FloorPlan.
- Skills: Javascript, TypeScript, Angular 12+, Vue 2, RxJs, NgRx Store, Vuex Store

FX3X - Skopje, North Macedonia— Vfx Roto Artist

August 2015 - May 2020 - 4 yrs 9 mos (On-site)

- Roto animation of movie footage from a given deadline.
- Proficiency in team work.
- Successful completion of the work within a given deadline.

EDUCATION

High School 'Pance Arsovski' - Skopje, North Macedonia

September 2008 - June 2012, Skopje

Online course for Frontend Web Developer - Skopje, North Macedonia

October 2020 - December 2020, FINKI - Skopje

PROJECTS

- <u>Annadaan Ammucare</u> Food donations for people or animals across India. Front end technologies: Javascript, Typescript, Angular/Ionic Framework
 - Web: <u>annadaan.ammucare</u>, Google Play Store: <u>annadaan.ammucare</u>
 - App Store: <u>annadaan.ammucare</u>
- Act 4 Hunger Food Donation ACT 4 Hunger (A4H) is a global charitable platform that serves food to the hungry. Front end technologies: Flutter(Dart), Riverpod
 - Google Play Store: act4hunger
 - App Store: <u>act4hunger</u>
- Reztor Renovation This project provides a powerful tool for managing jobs, assigning tasks, generating quotes and invoices, and to create perfect communication between team members. Front end technologies: Angular, Fuse Template, Tailwind CSS
- Serve Swiftly Building SaaS platform for restaurants, bars and similar companies in the Food & Beverages industry to reinvent the way they do order management. Some of the core features were orders, employee, work shift and product management. Front end

technologies: Flutter(Dart), Riverpod

• PULZ - Web project which is an Admin portal where doctors can login and review a patient's heart health history and download or preview raw ECG data for further processing and analysis.